rxpgonline.com 2013-08-19

# privacy [RxPG]

Writing /home/jrxpgaco/public_html/rxpgonline/docs/data/cache/d/d8ee9044a46619995582567e57bad6bd.i failed

Unable to save cache file. Hint: disk full; file permissions; safe_mode setting.

Writing /home/jrxpgaco/public_html/rxpgonline/docs/data/cache/d/d8ee9044a46619995582567e57bad6bd.xhtml failed

The following privacy policy applies to the usage of rxpgonline.com. The term “RxPG” used in this document refers to “RxPG Medical Solutions Private Limited, India” 

#### Privacy Statement for RxPG

RxPG has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for RxPG. 

#### Information Automatically Logged

RxPG use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer RxPG. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, to help cater RxPG's content to your needs and other site management issues. 

#### Cookies

RxPG sites can uses cookies to remember your login name and pass it between forms, so that you do not have to enter it on every page of database operation. Cookies are not used to automatically log you in to the website at every visit as we do not provide any remember me option on login . Whenever member sign in feature is used, the logout option is prominently displayed on every page and on being clicked will erase the cookies set in your computer. 

#### Advertisers

RxPG use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While RxPG use cookies in other parts of RxPG, cookies received with banner ads are collected by RxPG ad company, and RxPG do not have access to this information. 

#### Registration Forms

RxPG's registration form, if used, can require users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and sometimes postal address). The member's or customer's contact information is used to get in touch with them when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We don't share your email and personal information with any one unrelated to RxPG. 

#### External Links

RxPG might contain links to other sites. RxPG is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Public Forums

RxPG might make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Security

RxPG has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These include encryption of passwords when storing in the database, giving members-only access to the complete database (guests are limited to viewing names and batches only), and password driven access to change your details. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out

RxPG provides users the full opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. You can send email to [unsubscribe@rxpg.com](mailto:unsubscribe@rxpg.com "unsubscribe@rxpg.com"). Plus we give an option at sign up and later in your accounts section to opt out of our newsletters if any newsletter feature is used on RxPG. 

#### Data Quality/Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. To do so please visit <http://www.rxpgonline.com/modules.php?name=Your_Account>. You can also email to support@rxpg.com for specific issues with your data. 

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with RxPG, you can contact: [support@rxpg.com](mailto:support@rxpg.com "support@rxpg.com"). 

You can also use the contact us or feedback forums available on rxpgonline.com to ask us questions about our policies.
